  export const Data = [
    {
      question: 'How can I try Bonat?',
      answer: "You can request a demo from <a herf='#'>here</a> and our team will reach out to you."
    },
    {
      question: 'How can I subscribe to Bonat?',
      answer: 'Request a demo from here and our team will contact you to complete the subscription process.'
    },
    {
      question: 'How is Bonat Priced?',
      answer: 'Bonat subscription is a fixed monthly fee, for payment information please contact us here.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Are there other expenses?',
      answer: 'There is a onetime payment which includes tablet, stand, charger, establishment, and training. '
    },
    {
      question: 'Is there a trial period?',
      answer: 'Yes, there is a free 1-month fully refunded trial. '
    },
    {
      question: 'How can I subscribe for multiple branches?',
      answer: 'You can subscribe for as many branches as you have with an additional subscription and establishment fees.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Is there a cost or fee for the pickup service?',
      answer: 'Pickup service is free. Only bank commission is deducted from order.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Is there a cost or fee on coupon purchases in the Bonat store?',
      answer: 'Bonat store is free. Only bank commission is deducted from purchases. '
    },
    {
      question: 'How can I set up the rewards?',
      answer: 'You will have your own dashboard which will grant you full control to customize your reward menu.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Can I have multiple users in a subscription? ',
      answer: 'Yes. Through the dashboard you will be able to create different roles (e.g. marketing manager, branch manager, accountant etc.) with different permissions and access to sections in the dashboard.  You can assign different users to the role.'
    },


  ];